besttechguru.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy « Best Tech Guru

_We also advice our reader to read the[Disclaimer](http://www.besttechguru.com/disclaimer/ "Disclaimer") for detailed Terms and Conditions and User Agreement to use this website_

At “Best Tech Guru” we highly value your privacy. The only personal information that “Best Tech Guru” collects about you when you use our website is what you tell us about yourself voluntarily or information you provide to us through the Contact forms, Comments, Forums, Registrations or when you send us an e-mail.

As most websites do, however, we do track usage patterns on an anonymous basis. We may record your IP address, but, your identity cannot reasonably be ascertained from this information. Each time you visit our site, our server records your Internet Service Provider, the date and time of your visit, the pages you visit and the documents downloaded, the searches you performed, and the referring URLs you came from. We use this non-personal information to optimize our service.

At www.besttechguru.com , we allow Ad Companies to display advertisements on our website. Hence, “Best Tech Guru” readers and visitors are hereby informed that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your web browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on this website.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Please note that an advertiser may ask “Best Tech Guru” to show an ad to a certain audience of Users (e.g., based on demographics or other interests). In that situation, “Best Tech Guru” or our Partners determines the target audience and “Best Tech Guru” serves the advertising to that audience and only provides anonymous data to the advertiser. If you respond to such an ad, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

To enhance your user experience or help us improve and measure our effectiveness, “Best Tech Guru” may embed code from third parties on the Service. These third parties may collect information about you including IP address, cookies in ways “Best Tech Guru” does not control.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

The “Best Tech Guru” Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of third-parties. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such third parties or contact such third parties for more information.

### Newsletter Opt-Out Policy:

besttechguru.com offers a free electronic newsletter to users. “Best Tech Guru” gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove  themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that gives you the option to Unsubscribe from future emails and communications.

### Surveys And Opinion Polls:

From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Legal Disclaimer:

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our website.

“Best Tech Guru” may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this page.

_This Privacy Policy was  last modified on April 23rd 2015._
